const questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which team won the ICC Men’s T20 World Cup in 2024?",
        answer: "India",
        options: [
            "India",
            "Australia",
            "Afganistan",
            "South Africa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Who was the highest run-scorer in the tournament?",
        answer: "Rahmanullah Gurbaz (AFG)",
        options: [
            "Rohit Sharma (IND)",
            "Rahmanullah Gurbaz (AFG)",
            "Quinton de Kock (SA)",
            "Babar Azam (PAK)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which bowler took the most wickets in the T20 World Cup 2024?",
        answer: "Fazalhaq Farooqi (AFG)",
        options: ["Kagiso Rabada (SA)", "Jasprit Bumrah (IND)", "Fazalhaq Farooqi (AFG)", "Anrich Nortje (SA)"]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which player hit the most sixes during the T20 World Cup 2024?",
        answer: "Nicholas Pooran (WI)",
        options: ["Rohit Sharma (IND)", "Travis Head (AUS)", "Nicholas Pooran (WI)", "Rahmanullah Gurbaz (AFG)"]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Who was the leading wicket-keeper in terms of dismissals (catches and stumpings) during the tournament?",
        answer: "Rishabh Pant (IND)",
        options: ["Quinton de Kock (SA)", "Jos Buttler (ENG)", "Tim Seifert (NZ)", "Rishabh Pant (IND)"]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which team scored the highest team total in a single match during the T20 World Cup 2024?",
        answer: "West Indies",
        options: ["India", "West Indies", "Afganistan", "South Africa"]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Who won the Player of the Tournament award in the Men’s T20 World Cup 2024?",
        answer: "Jasprit Bumrah (IND)",
        options: ["Johnson Charles (WI)", "Glenn Maxwell (AUS)", "Hardik Pandya (IND)", "Jasprit Bumrah (IND)"]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which player hit the most fours during the T20 World Cup 2024?",
        answer: "Travis Head (AUS)",
        options: ["Ibrahim Zadran (AFG)", "Travis Head (AUS)", "Rahmanullah Gurbaz (AFG)", "Quinton de Kock (SA)"]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which was the venue of Men’s T20 World Cup 2024 Final?",
        answer: "Kensington Oval",
        options: ["Kensington Oval", "Central Broward Park", "Grand Prairie Stadium", "Queen's Park Oval"]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which player scored highest individual score of Men’s T20 World Cup in 2024?",
        answer: "Nicholas Pooran (WI)",
        options: ["Nicholas Pooran (WI)", "Aaron Jones (USA)", "Rohit Sharma (IND)", "Phil Salt (ENG)"]
    }
]